let gkQuestions = [
    {
    question: "Which of these is NOT an Australian state or territory?"

    choice1: "Alberta"
    choice2: "New South Wales"
    choice3: "Victoria"
    choice4: "Queensland"
    answer:1
    },

    {
    question: "Where is the Jubilee House located in Ghana?"
    choice1 :"Kumasi"
    choice2 :"Accra"
    choice3 : "Tema"
    choice4 : "Prampram"
    answer : 2
    },
    {
    question: "In what year did the Wall Street Crash take place?"
    choice1: "1929"
    choice2: "1932"
    choice3: "1930"
    choice4: "1925"
    answer: 1
    },
    {
    quesion: "What is considered the rarest form of color blindness?"
    choice1: "Blue"
    choice2: "Red"
    choice3: "Green"
    choice4: "Purple"
    answer: 2
    },
    {
    question: "Which ocean borders the southern coast of the Ghana?"
    choice1: "Pacific"
    choice2: "Atlantic"
    choice3: "Indian"
    choice4: "Arctic"
    answer: 2
    },
    {
    question: "Which is the largest man-made lake in West Africa?"
    choice1: "Lake Victoria"
    choice2: "Lake Volta"
    choice3: "Lake Michigan"
    choice4: "Lake Huron"
    answer: 2
    },
    {
    question: "Rock, Paper, ........"  
    choice1: "pen"
    choice2: "scissors"
    choice3: "knife"
    choice4: "scissors"
    answer : 4
    },
    {
    question: "Cats meow, goats bleet, frogs........?"
    choice1: "bark"
    choice2: "leap"
    choice3: "croak"
    choice4: "jump"
    answer: 3
    }
]

let csQuestions = [
    {
    question: "In c++, which type of error does not generate compiler warnings? " 
    choice1: "runtime exceptions"
    choice2: "semantic error"
    choice3: "syntactic error"
    choice4: "grammatic error"
    answer: 2

    },
    {
    question: "JSON stands for?"
    choice1: "Java Standard Output Network"
    choice2:"JavaScript Object Notation"
    choice3:"JavaScript Output Name"
    choice4:"Java Source Open Network"
    answer: 2
    },
    {

    question: "Which one of these Programming languages is\"loosely typed\" ?"
    choice1: "C"
    choice2: "C++"
    choice3: "Python"
    choice4: "Java"
    answer: 3
    },
    {
    question:"Which of these is an acess modifier"
    choice1: "int"
    choice2: "private"
    choice3: "float"
    choice4: "double"
    answer: 
    },
    {
    question: "what is a constructor in OOP?"
    choice1: "A method used in instantiating ant class"
    choice1: "A primitive datatype"
    choice3: "An abstract datatype"
    choice4: "None of the above"
    answer: "1"
    },
    {
    question:"what is the study of techniques that hide the true meaning of information  called? "
    choice1: "Digital signal processing"
    choice2: "Cryptography"
    choice3: "Numerology"
    choice4: "None of the above"
    answer: 2
    },
]
mathQuestions=[
    {
        question:"Evaluate 3*9^(1/2)"
        choice1: "5"
        choice2: "9"
        choice3: "7.5"
        choice4: "18"
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question:"what is the area of a circle of radius r, and diameter d?"
        choice1: "pi*(d^2)/4"
        choice2: "2*(pi/2)*r^2"
        choice3: "pi*r^2"
        choice4: "All the above" 
    },
    {
        question:"Find the diagonal length of a square of breadth 1 unit."
        choice1: "2"
        choice2: "4"
        choice3: "2^(1/2)"
        choice4: "3"
        answer:3
    },
        question:"Evaluate 3-2*4+7"
        choice1: "11"
        choice2: "2"
        choice3: "6"
        choice4: "9"
        answer:2
]


